Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Irish Legislature, 1985-1992 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Irish American Labor Coalition, 1985-1991 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - ICTU, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Ireland, 1993-1995 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Ireland: Gerry Adams, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Centennial of Irish Trade Unions, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Consulate General of Ireland, 1986-1992 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Ireland Trip, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Irish American Cultural Center, 1987-1990 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Ireland Trip, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Iron Workers, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Italian American Labor Council, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Italian Cultural Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Israel Trip, 1985-1990 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - ITT Meyer Industries, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Jamestown Area Labor Council, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Japan Trip, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Javitz Center, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Jeanie Johnston Project, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Jefferson, Lewis, and St. Lawrence Counties, Central Trades and Labor Council, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Roger Jepsen, Senator, Iowa, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Federal Jobs Opportunities List, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - New York Job Development Authority, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Job Bills, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Job Development Authority, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Job Service Funding Reductions, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Job Service Program, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Job Training, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - John Jay College, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Joint Council on Economic Education, 1984-1989 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Greater Jamaica Development Corp., 1987 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Joe Jamison Research Department, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - John Jay College of Criminal Justice, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Jesuit Office, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Jewish National Fund of NY, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Job Stabilization Bill, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Justice and Peace Commission of Rockville Centre, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - The Kamber Group, 1989-1993 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Kingboro Community College, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Lane Kirkland, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - John Kelly Dinner, Local 153, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Harry Kelber Empowerment in Labor Studies, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Kentucky State AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Keystone Club of the Electrical Industry of NYC, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Kleinberg Electric, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Korea Trade Unions, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Laborers International Union, 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Labor Hall of Fame, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Labor Liaison, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Labor/Management Conference, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - Labor Action Coalition of New York, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - Labor Desk Tour: Colleen Crawford, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - Labor Laws, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - Labor Net AFL-CIO, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - Labor News and Commentary, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - Labor Management Commission Statewide, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Labor Management Structures in the Large City Ahern, Robert, undated (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - Laid-off Workers, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - Labor Research Association, 1987-1992 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - Labor Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Labor Fights Back, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Labor History, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Labor and Investment, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Labor Trends, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - The Center for Labor & Urban Programs, Research & Analysis: Herbert Beinstock, Director, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - La Guardia Community College, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Labor Women, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Senator James Lack, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Latin American Labor Council, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Latin America, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Law Affecting Labor Union, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Conference Education Fund, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Las Vegas Strike (Hotels), 1984 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Lehigh Portland Cemetery, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Leichter, Franz S., Senator, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Lesson Plan Competition, undated (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Leadership Training Manual, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - League on Women Voters, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Bill Drafting Committee, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Gazette, undated (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - License Plates, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Legitech, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Letter Carriers, NYS Association, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Leverage by Outs, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Lewiston-Porter Commencement Address, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Lie Detections, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - LILCO, undated (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Livery Car Drivers, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Local 153 Health Fund and Contracts, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Lobbyist List, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Long Island Correctional Facility, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Long Island Action Plan, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporations, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Long Island Labor Religion Coalition, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Louisiana State AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Machinists, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Mailing Privileges, How to Apply, undated (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Paul N. Mallon Company, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Department of Labor, Maine, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Maine AFL-CIO Conference, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Manhattanville College, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Manhattan Community College, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Managed Care, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Manpower Institute, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Manufacturing, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 49)
  - Maritime Industry, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 50)
  - Maritime Ports Council, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 51)
  - Marriott Hotels and Resorts, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 52)
  - Maryland Department of Economic and Community Development, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 53)
  - Marymount Manhattan College, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 54)
  - Mason Tenders, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 55)
  - Mass Electric of New York, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 56)
  - Massachusetts Power Plants, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 57)
  - The Commonwealth of MA, undated (Box 69, Folder 58)
  - Massachusetts AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 59)
  - Medicaid, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 60)
  - Membership Statistics, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 61)
  - MEDCO, undated (Box 69, Folder 62)
  - Metro Labor List, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Opera, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - MTA Capitol Program, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Michigan ALF-CIO, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - East Michigan University, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Dan Miller Photography, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Lorraine, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Minimum Wage, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Minnesota AFL-CIO, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Minority Business Program in New York State, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Minority Gains in New York Construction Jobs, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Missouri State Labor Council, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Molinassi, Howard, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Monday Comments, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Montana AFL-CIO, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Monticello Raceway, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Moral Re-armament, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Morrisania Hospital Property, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Senator Moinahan, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Multistate Industrial Retention Commission, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Movers, Minority Organizers, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Musicians, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Benito Mussolini, undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - NAFTA, 1993-1995 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - NAFTA, 1991-1993 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - National Apprentice Program, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - NABET National Association of Broadcast Employees, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - NADAP, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - National Save American Industry Jobs Day, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Nassau Suffolks Contractors Association, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Parliamentary, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Puerto Ricans Civil Rights, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - National Center for Vision and Aging, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - The National Conference of Christian and Jews, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - National Issues Seminar: National Conference of State Legislatures, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - National and Community Trust Act of 1993 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - National Employment Priorities Act, undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - National Fuel, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - National Football League, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - National Democratic Convention, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - National Organizing Committee, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - National Organization for Women, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - National Rifle Association, undated (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - National Right to Work Committee, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - National Safety Council, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - National Transportation Policy, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - National Highway System, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - New England Energy, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Nevada AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - New England Labor News and Commentary, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - New Hampshire AFL-CIO, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - New Initiatives for New Employment, undated (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - State of New Jersey, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - NJ State Fed. 21st Constitutional Convention, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - NJ State AFL-CIO Conference, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - New School for Social Research, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - New York Air Brake Co., 1985 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - New York City Apprentice Program for the Economically Disadvantaged, 1987-1997 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - New York State Association of Electrical Contractors, 1987-1992 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Business Trends in New York State, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - City of New York Department of Buildings, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - New York Building Congress, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - New York City Central Labor Rehabilitation Council, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - New York Civil Union NYCLU, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - New York Harbor, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - NY COSH, 1984-1989 (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - New York Employee Assistance Program, undated (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - New York Construction Users Council, undated (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - New York Consumer Assembly, undated (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - New York Office Fire Wardens, undated (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - City of New York Correspondence, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - New York Housing Partnership, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - New York Coliseum, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - New York Compact, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - New York City Convention Center, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - NYC Department of Investigation, 1986-1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - NYC Labor Committee, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - NYC Planning Commission, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Public Works New York City, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - NYC Labor/Religion Coalition, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - New York S.O.S. Model Plank on Social Security, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - NY Step Program, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - New York Times, 1986-1991 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Ideas for a Better New York, draft, confidential, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - NYS and the Federal FISC, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - New York Office of the Aging, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - NYS Apprenticeship Council Affirmative Action Implementation, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - NYS Assembly Labor Committee Statement on Unemployment, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - NYS Labor Committee Legislative Priorities, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - NYS Assembly Incentive Programs for Public Employees, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - New York State Association of Counties, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - NYS Attorney General, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - NYS Bankers Association, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - New York State Bar Association, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - New York Bond Issue Act, undated (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Executive Budget Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - NYS Budget, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - NYS Budget Director, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - NYS Building and Construction Trade Council, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - NYS Council of Carpenters, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - NYS Coastal Management Advisory Committee of the Maritime Industry, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - NYS Department of Civil Service, 1989-1992 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - NYS Department of Commerce, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Commercial Divers Program, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - NYS Comptroller, 1988-1994 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - NYCOM, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - NYS Democratic Party, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - NYS New Democratic Coalition, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - NYS Dormitory Authority, 1989-1991 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - NY Department of Economic Development: Advisory Council, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - NYS Department of Economic Development: Defense Advisory Panel, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - NYC Fiscal Economic Future, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - New York State Department of Education, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - NYS Education Department: Adult Learning Week, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - NYS Higher Education Services Corporation, 1984-1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - NYS PERB, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - NYS Employees Retirement Service, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - NYS Energy Plan, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - NYS Equal Rights Amendment Group, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - NYS Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - NYS Farmworkers, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - NYS Festival, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - NYS Gasoline Tax, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Governors Office of Employee Relation, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - NYS Office of General Services, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - MYS Department of Health, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - NY Council of Health Care Financing, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - NYS Department of Health, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - NYS Highway System, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - The State of the City Housing Initiatives, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - State Human Investment Program, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - NYS Human Advisory Board Council, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Rockefeller Institute, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - NYS Insurance Department, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - NYS Insurance Fund Reporter, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - NYS Interagency Task Force on Insurance, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Industrial Labor Union Department, 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - NYS Commission of Investigations, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - NYS Committee for Jobs and Independence, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - NYS Investment and Employment Tax Credits, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - NYS Job Bond Act, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - NYS Statewide Labor-Management Committee, undated (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - New York Post, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - NYS Labor/Religion Coalition, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - State of New York Department of Labor, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - NYS Department of Labor Layoffs and Firings, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - NYS Unemployment Insurance and Employment Services Programs, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - NYS Prevailing Wage Law: Investigative Analysis, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - NYS Department of Labor: Jobs Application, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - NYS Employment Trends, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - NYS Department of Labor News, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - NYS Department of Labor Prevailing News, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - NYS DOL National Economic Commission, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - NYS Department of Law, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - NYS Labor Law, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - NYS Office of Lieutenant Governor, 1990-1992 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - NYS State Commission of Lobbying, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - NYS Lottery Commission, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - NYS Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officials, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - NYS Nurses Association, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - NYS Occupational Information Coordinating Committee, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - NYS Occupational Retraining and Re-Employment Act, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - NYS OSHA Hazard Abatement Board, 1990-1992 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Office of Business Permits and Regulatory Assistance, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - NYC for Occupational Education, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - NYS Pension Task Force, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Policy Committee of the NYS Occupational Disease Study Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - NYS Petroleum Council, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - NYS State Police, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - New York Power Authority, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - NYS Police Center at CUNY, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - NYS Power Authority, 1977-1989 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - NYS Professional Firefighters Association, 1985-1992 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - NYS Public Employee Federation, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - NYS Public Employee Conference, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - NYS Public Employee Pension System: Advisory Council, 1988-1992 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - NYS Public Employment Relations Board, 1988-1990 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - NYS Commission on Public Management Systems, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - New York/New Jersey Harbor, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - NYS Public Sector Coalition on Health Benefits, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - NYS Public Sector Work Task Force in the 21st Century, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - NYS Public Sector Labor-Management Consortium, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - NYS School to Employment Program, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - NYS Senate Standing Committee on Labor, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - NYS Council of Senior Citizens, 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - NYS Senate Committee on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - New York State Senate, undated (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Senate Committee on Environmental Works, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - NY Department of Social Services, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - NYS State of the Child, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - NY Department of the State, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - NYS Division of Substance Abuse Services, 1988-1991 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - NYS Supreme Court Officers Association, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - NY Subway Advertising Company, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - NYS Tax Equity Coalition, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - State Tax Reduction Windfall Tax, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - NYS Department of Taxation and Finance, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - NYS Department of Transportation, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - NYS Vacancy Listings of Boards and Commissions, 1983-1987 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Gov. Task Force on Work and Family, 1987-1991 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Letters to Gov. Cuomo with responses, 1989-1991 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - NYS United Teachers, 1984-1989 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - NYS Urban Development Corp., 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - New York University, 1985-1992 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1995 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Niagara-Orleans, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Niagara Hydropower Plant, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Nolan, Catherine, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Non-Traditional Employment for Women, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina AFL-CIO, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - The Niagara Hilton, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - North Star Contracting Corp., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1989 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear Information, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Occupational Clinics, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Local 153 OPEIU Health Fund, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Local 153 OPEIU Contract, 1985-1994 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Ohio State University News, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Oklahoma State AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Omni/Albany Hotel, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Omnibus Abuse Act of 1988 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - One-on-One, undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Onodaga County Convention Center, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Op Ed., 1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Opportunity Zones, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Options for the Disposition of the World Trade Center, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Oregon AFLCIO, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - ORT Israel, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - George Pataki, 1985-1993 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Painters and Allied Trades, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Peace and World Studies Order, A Curriculum Guide, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Peterson, William, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, 1994-1990 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Pension Investments, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Pension Task Force List of Members, undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Pension Task Force, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Pension Funds, 1985-1990 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Pension Investment Policy Group, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Pension Supplementation, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - The Peoples Lobby: An AFL-CIO Report on the 97th Congress, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Persian Gulf, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Congressmen Peter Geyser, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Phelph Dodge Strike Arizona, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Philippine Trade Union Movement, undated (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Plant Closings, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Plumbers, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Police Conference of New York, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Political Action Committees, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Polygraph Tests, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Pope John Pauls Encyclical Laborem Exercens on Human Labor, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Postal Workers, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Poverty, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Power Plants, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Prentice Hall, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Precision Arts, Inc., undated (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - The Preservation League, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Prevailing Wages, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Prevailing Wages: San Francisco International Airport, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - PIC, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Price Choppers UFCW, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Prison Labor, 1993-1995 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Prison Industry, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Private Industries, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Private Industry Conference, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Privatization, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Pro Bono Advisors, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Procurement Reform in NYS Government, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Product Liability, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Professional Staff Conference, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)